{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955725059","data":{"timestamp":" 946955725059"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955725281","data":{"timestamp":" 946955725281"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955726245","data":{"timestamp":" 946955726245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955727517","data":{"timestamp":" 946955727517"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955730375","data":{"timestamp":" 946955730375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955731218","data":{"timestamp":" 946955731218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955731531","data":{"timestamp":" 946955731531"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955732764","data":{"timestamp":" 946955732764"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955736255","data":{"timestamp":" 946955736255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955737245","data":{"timestamp":" 946955737245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955737498","data":{"timestamp":" 946955737498"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955738441","data":{"timestamp":" 946955738441"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955741277","data":{"timestamp":" 946955741277"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955742310","data":{"timestamp":" 946955742310"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955742784","data":{"timestamp":" 946955742784"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955747304","data":{"timestamp":" 946955747304"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955747378","data":{"timestamp":" 946955747378"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 0e2187fa-df62-4aba-8ca2-7d5ceb4c9129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955756109","data":{"timestamp":" 946955756109"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955756332","data":{"timestamp":" 946955756332"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955757296","data":{"timestamp":" 946955757296"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955758569","data":{"timestamp":" 946955758569"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955761441","data":{"timestamp":" 946955761441"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955762285","data":{"timestamp":" 946955762285"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955762598","data":{"timestamp":" 946955762597"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955763832","data":{"timestamp":" 946955763832"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955767324","data":{"timestamp":" 946955767324"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955768307","data":{"timestamp":" 946955768307"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955768559","data":{"timestamp":" 946955768559"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955769504","data":{"timestamp":" 946955769503"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955772348","data":{"timestamp":" 946955772348"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955773382","data":{"timestamp":" 946955773381"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955773855","data":{"timestamp":" 946955773855"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955778357","data":{"timestamp":" 946955778356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955778439","data":{"timestamp":" 946955778438"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955786252","data":{"timestamp":" 946955786251"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b54042da-bbeb-45a9-9d90-e14977e74d5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955822462","data":{"timestamp":" 946955822462"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 879f804f-be8a-4a0c-ae1a-dc864be0441c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_545_545-842-865"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 545"," userResponse":" 545"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955843354","data":{"timestamp":" 946955843354"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 879f804f-be8a-4a0c-ae1a-dc864be0441c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_706_706-684-478"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 706"," userResponse":" 706"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955887346","data":{"timestamp":" 946955887345"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 879f804f-be8a-4a0c-ae1a-dc864be0441c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_706_706-684-478"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955899338","data":{"timestamp":" 946955899338"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 879f804f-be8a-4a0c-ae1a-dc864be0441c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_706_706-684-478"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955908797","data":{"timestamp":" 946955908797"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955909019","data":{"timestamp":" 946955909019"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955909983","data":{"timestamp":" 946955909983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955911255","data":{"timestamp":" 946955911255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955914104","data":{"timestamp":" 946955914104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955914948","data":{"timestamp":" 946955914948"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955915261","data":{"timestamp":" 946955915261"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955916493","data":{"timestamp":" 946955916493"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955919973","data":{"timestamp":" 946955919972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955920956","data":{"timestamp":" 946955920956"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955921209","data":{"timestamp":" 946955921208"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955922154","data":{"timestamp":" 946955922154"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955924983","data":{"timestamp":" 946955924983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955926017","data":{"timestamp":" 946955926017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955926489","data":{"timestamp":" 946955926489"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955931020","data":{"timestamp":" 946955931019"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955931097","data":{"timestamp":" 946955931096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955937537","data":{"timestamp":" 946955937536"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:673..773.off10.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955998981","data":{"timestamp":" 946955998980"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956010710","data":{"timestamp":" 946956010710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956017907","data":{"timestamp":" 946956017907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956023737","data":{"timestamp":" 946956023737"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:673..773.off10.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956030467","data":{"timestamp":" 946956030467"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956036536","data":{"timestamp":" 946956036536"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956042588","data":{"timestamp":" 946956042587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956048206","data":{"timestamp":" 946956048206"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:673..773.off10.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956058339","data":{"timestamp":" 946956058339"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956065826","data":{"timestamp":" 946956065826"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1f937462-d0de-4c5e-8b0d-000dfb2f98b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956074969","data":{"timestamp":" 946956074968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956075200","data":{"timestamp":" 946956075200"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956076176","data":{"timestamp":" 946956076176"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956077469","data":{"timestamp":" 946956077469"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956080436","data":{"timestamp":" 946956080436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956081290","data":{"timestamp":" 946956081289"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956081609","data":{"timestamp":" 946956081609"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956082854","data":{"timestamp":" 946956082852"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956084993","data":{"timestamp":" 946956084992"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956085054","data":{"timestamp":" 946956085054"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956090383","data":{"timestamp":" 946956090382"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:673..773.off10.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956096230","data":{"timestamp":" 946956096230"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956101833","data":{"timestamp":" 946956101832"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956110898","data":{"timestamp":" 946956110897"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956116814","data":{"timestamp":" 946956116814"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:673..773.off10.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956123384","data":{"timestamp":" 946956123384"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956133596","data":{"timestamp":" 946956133596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956141422","data":{"timestamp":" 946956141421"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956147008","data":{"timestamp":" 946956147007"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:673..773.off10.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956152210","data":{"timestamp":" 946956152209"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956160488","data":{"timestamp":" 946956160487"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956166175","data":{"timestamp":" 946956166175"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956176804","data":{"timestamp":" 946956176804"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 9a9b2db3-3c0f-4b86-909e-4644392c664f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956191968","data":{"timestamp":" 946956191968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_709_472-709-687"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 709"," userResponse":" 709"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956201123","data":{"timestamp":" 946956201123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_706_706-684-478"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 706"," userResponse":" 706"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956212457","data":{"timestamp":" 946956212457"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_559_435-723-559"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 559"," userResponse":" 559"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956226669","data":{"timestamp":" 946956226669"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_888_888-468-486"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 888"," userResponse":" 888"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956250938","data":{"timestamp":" 946956250938"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_659_554-659-796"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 659"," userResponse":" 659"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956296095","data":{"timestamp":" 946956296094"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_416_416-689-579"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 416"," userResponse":" 416"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956308818","data":{"timestamp":" 946956308818"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_872_872-641-810"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 872"," userResponse":" 810"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956317230","data":{"timestamp":" 946956317230"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_872_872-641-810"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 872"," userResponse":" 872"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956334804","data":{"timestamp":" 946956334804"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_484_657-484-687"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 484"," userResponse":" 484"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956352030","data":{"timestamp":" 946956352030"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_768_768-682-600"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 768"," userResponse":" 768"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956372830","data":{"timestamp":" 946956372830"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_698_698-747-806"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 698"," userResponse":" 747"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956382706","data":{"timestamp":" 946956382706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_698_698-747-806"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 698"," userResponse":" 698"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956392344","data":{"timestamp":" 946956392344"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_698_698-747-806"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956398264","data":{"timestamp":" 946956398263"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_698_698-747-806"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956407121","data":{"timestamp":" 946956407121"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_698_698-747-806"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956412870","data":{"timestamp":" 946956412869"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" ab1e8e97-ec29-4d86-a5c5-0a335a298254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL3.decr.90"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_698_698-747-806"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956428364","data":{"timestamp":" 946956428364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 39669b0a-3378-4659-a964-2e20b66c1971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_439_456-506-439"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 439"," userResponse":" 456"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956437900","data":{"timestamp":" 946956437900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 39669b0a-3378-4659-a964-2e20b66c1971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_439_456-506-439"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 439"," userResponse":" 439"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956450986","data":{"timestamp":" 946956450986"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 39669b0a-3378-4659-a964-2e20b66c1971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_719_652-807-719"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 719"," userResponse":" 719"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956472021","data":{"timestamp":" 946956472020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 39669b0a-3378-4659-a964-2e20b66c1971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_719_652-807-719"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956477270","data":{"timestamp":" 946956477270"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 39669b0a-3378-4659-a964-2e20b66c1971"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.91"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_719_652-807-719"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956486468","data":{"timestamp":" 946956486468"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956486691","data":{"timestamp":" 946956486690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956487661","data":{"timestamp":" 946956487660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956488948","data":{"timestamp":" 946956488947"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956491833","data":{"timestamp":" 946956491833"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956492693","data":{"timestamp":" 946956492692"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956493013","data":{"timestamp":" 946956493012"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956494256","data":{"timestamp":" 946956494255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956497873","data":{"timestamp":" 946956497872"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956498873","data":{"timestamp":" 946956498872"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956499140","data":{"timestamp":" 946956499140"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956500097","data":{"timestamp":" 946956500096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956503005","data":{"timestamp":" 946956503005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956504048","data":{"timestamp":" 946956504048"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956504528","data":{"timestamp":" 946956504528"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956507031","data":{"timestamp":" 946956507031"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956507111","data":{"timestamp":" 946956507111"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" eb08789a-ad9f-49c6-aa03-9bc44868a94e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956517333","data":{"timestamp":" 946956517333"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956518981","data":{"timestamp":" 946956518980"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956520741","data":{"timestamp":" 946956520741"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956520842","data":{"timestamp":" 946956520842"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956522037","data":{"timestamp":" 946956522037"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956522808","data":{"timestamp":" 946956522801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956522898","data":{"timestamp":" 946956522898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 91ee98bf-ef3f-4248-84ec-e6f7559a823e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956543775","data":{"timestamp":" 946956543775"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 437"," userResponse":" 597"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956568322","data":{"timestamp":" 946956568322"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956573206","data":{"timestamp":" 946956573206"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956579346","data":{"timestamp":" 946956579346"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956585282","data":{"timestamp":" 946956585282"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956597684","data":{"timestamp":" 946956597683"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956602058","data":{"timestamp":" 946956602058"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956607180","data":{"timestamp":" 946956607179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956612844","data":{"timestamp":" 946956612843"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956642368","data":{"timestamp":" 946956642368"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956649200","data":{"timestamp":" 946956649200"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956655024","data":{"timestamp":" 946956655024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956660519","data":{"timestamp":" 946956660519"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956671266","data":{"timestamp":" 946956671266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956675937","data":{"timestamp":" 946956675937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956681780","data":{"timestamp":" 946956681780"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956692635","data":{"timestamp":" 946956692634"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956701900","data":{"timestamp":" 946956701900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956708483","data":{"timestamp":" 946956708483"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956714623","data":{"timestamp":" 946956714622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956728066","data":{"timestamp":" 946956728066"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956749103","data":{"timestamp":" 946956749103"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956759585","data":{"timestamp":" 946956759585"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956765276","data":{"timestamp":" 946956765275"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956770957","data":{"timestamp":" 946956770957"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL2.incr.75","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956778330","data":{"timestamp":" 946956778330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956783851","data":{"timestamp":" 946956783850"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956789592","data":{"timestamp":" 946956789592"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956794993","data":{"timestamp":" 946956794993"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956845492","data":{"timestamp":" 946956845492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956851454","data":{"timestamp":" 946956851454"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956858572","data":{"timestamp":" 946956858570"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956864034","data":{"timestamp":" 946956864033"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956879079","data":{"timestamp":" 946956879078"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956886161","data":{"timestamp":" 946956886161"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956891919","data":{"timestamp":" 946956891918"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956898683","data":{"timestamp":" 946956898682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956908046","data":{"timestamp":" 946956908046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956913057","data":{"timestamp":" 946956913057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956919613","data":{"timestamp":" 946956919612"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956926051","data":{"timestamp":" 946956926050"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956937556","data":{"timestamp":" 946956937555"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 98d3893f-b523-49f5-b4e3-7a939028e526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.92"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_437_597-437-604"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957047218","data":{"timestamp":" 946957047218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_135_818-295-135"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 135"," userResponse":" 135"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957066607","data":{"timestamp":" 946957066607"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 355"," userResponse":" 367"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957093322","data":{"timestamp":" 946957093322"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 355"," userResponse":" 355"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957101853","data":{"timestamp":" 946957101853"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957110585","data":{"timestamp":" 946957110585"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957116828","data":{"timestamp":" 946957116827"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957123343","data":{"timestamp":" 946957123343"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957173420","data":{"timestamp":" 946957173419"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 1c3f817d-5b89-4106-8455-ffa2d7662d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_355_355-238-367"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957185547","data":{"timestamp":" 946957185547"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b436026d-3a55-4969-92b9-69515b0e3262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957190681","data":{"timestamp":" 946957190681"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b436026d-3a55-4969-92b9-69515b0e3262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957190827","data":{"timestamp":" 946957190827"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" b436026d-3a55-4969-92b9-69515b0e3262"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957203350","data":{"timestamp":" 946957203350"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957203584","data":{"timestamp":" 946957203584"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957204558","data":{"timestamp":" 946957204557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957205843","data":{"timestamp":" 946957205843"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957208795","data":{"timestamp":" 946957208795"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957209639","data":{"timestamp":" 946957209639"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957209952","data":{"timestamp":" 946957209952"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957211193","data":{"timestamp":" 946957211193"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957214690","data":{"timestamp":" 946957214690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957215674","data":{"timestamp":" 946957215674"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957215927","data":{"timestamp":" 946957215927"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957216870","data":{"timestamp":" 946957216870"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957219726","data":{"timestamp":" 946957219726"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957220761","data":{"timestamp":" 946957220761"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957221235","data":{"timestamp":" 946957221235"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957225769","data":{"timestamp":" 946957225768"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957225964","data":{"timestamp":" 946957225964"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957232566","data":{"timestamp":" 946957232566"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957254224","data":{"timestamp":" 946957254224"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_061510"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}